https://www.walnuthollow.com/service/privacy-policy/

Recently Viewed
You have not viewed any products recently.
Privacy Policy
We Respect Your Privacy!
It may be the fine print written by our lawyer, but it's still important.  We're dedicated to protecting your privacy.
Walnut Hollow Farm, Inc. ("Walnut Hollow," "we," "us”) respects your privacy, including the privacy of your information his Privacy Policy explains what information we collect through our website at www.walnuthollow.com (the "Site") and our other Services, and how we use this information to provide outstanding service to you.
By accessing and using the Site or other Services owned and/or operated by Walnut Hollow (collectively, the "Services"), you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services.
If you feel that Walnut Hollow is not abiding by this Privacy Policy, you should contact us. Walnut Hollow's offices are located at 1409 State Road 23, Dodgeville WI 53533. We will do our best to resolve your inquiry.
This policy was last updated: 05/30/12
1. Information Collected Through Our Services
We gather two basic types of information through the Services: personally identifiable information that identifies a person as an individual ("Personal Information") and non-personally identifiable information, which includes aggregated information, demographic information, IP addresses and any other information that does not reveal a person's specific identity ("Non-Personal Information").
a. Personal Information - You do not have to provide Personal Information to use the Site. However, you may need to provide certain Personal Information to use some of our other Services. For example, when you sign up with Walnut Hollow, you establish a password-protected personal account for using our other Services. In order to establish your Walnut Hollow account, we will need your name, email address and password. (The password will allow you access to your account; as such, it needs to be as secure as possible. A good password includes seemingly random letters and numbers, and isn't obvious (as an example, we do not suggest using names of a spouse, child, or pet). Additionally, when you order products or other paid products or services, we will need the shipping address, billing name and address, as well as the credit card number and expiration date (processed and authorized through Authorize.Net).
b. Non-Personal Information - When you visit and interact with the Services, we and our service providers and business partners may collect Non-Personal Information from sources such as server log files, environmental variables (such as your MAC address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, OS version, Internet browser, and Internet browser version) and from scanning navigational data to collect Non-Personal Information about our users in order to help us deliver better service and user experience. Such Non-Personal Information could include the web site you were on before coming to Walnut Hollow, IP addresses, or areas of site being clicked on most frequently. We and our service providers (including ad servers, outbound email vendors, affiliate vendors and search engine advertising agencies, and providers of web analytics tools) and business partners may also use "cookies" as well as so-called "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs" and other similar technologies to help us deliver better service and user experience and to facilitate your ongoing access to and use of our Services. Cookies are small data files stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of a particular cookie, or cookies from a particular website, to your computer. If you choose to reject all cookies, you may not be able to access the Services.
2. How We Use the Information We Collect
a. Personal Information - We may use Personal Information in the following ways:
i. Fulfillment of Requests - We may use Personal Information to fulfill the purpose for which such Personal Information was provided (e.g., to fulfill your purchase or other transaction).
ii. Administrative Communications - From time to time, we may send you service announcement updates with important information about Walnut Hollow. Service announcements may contain information vital to your account, so members may not unsubscribe from service announcements.
iii. Other Communications - We may notify you via email or through the mail about new features, products and promotions. We may also send you information on carefully screened third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you. If you wish to unsubscribe from these mailings, please review the instructions in the Section 6 ("Opt-Out") below.
iv. Contests and Surveys - We may occasionally request Personal Information through surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. The Personal Information collected is only used for purposes of improving user satisfaction with Walnut Hollow products and services, or in some cases, to notify winners and to deliver prizes. No Personal Information collected through these means is shared with or available to other third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes.
v. Testimonials - Testimonials are used to show benefits to certain programs Walnut Hollow offers. Walnut Hollow always seeks consent prior to posting any testimonial in which Personal Information is included.
vi. Customer Service - Any Personal Information obtained through your contact with our Customer Service team or communications with us, such as chat or emails, may be recorded to help us provide better service.
vii. Internal Business Purposes - We may also use Personal Information about you for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits and so forth.
viii. Friends and Family - Walnut Hollow Services allows you to send an email invitation to your selected recipients, to allow them to view, save, or purchase products. The email also may include information about special promotional offers from Walnut Hollow and/or carefully-screened third parties.
ix. Combining Information - At times, we may combine Personal Information collected from our Services and other information you shared with us to customize our service to you and improve your experience. For example, we may recommend products or offers you may be interested in based on what you have liked in the past, or remind you that you have an "active" shopping cart waiting for you. Additionally, in order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the Personal Information you submitted to us with information from third party sources.
b. Non-Personal Information - Because Non-Personal Information does not personally identify you, we may use such information for any purpose. In addition, we reserve the right to share Non-Personal Information, which does not personally identify you, with third parties, for any purpose. In some instances, we may combine Non-Personal Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographic location). If we do combine any Non-Personal Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined.
3. Disclosures of Personal Information
a. Third Party Service Providers - Walnut Hollow shares Personal Information with carefully screened third-party service providers to provide you with the products, services and information you have requested. Examples of such third-party service providers are credit card authorization companies, merchandise distributors and shippers. Please refer to each third-party service provider’s privacy policy and terms of use for more information.
b. Third Party Products and Services - Walnut Hollow also may share Personal Information with third parties to allow such third parties to provide you with the products, services and information that you have requested. This could include, but is not limited to packages of discounts, rebates, and promotional offers, that are not Walnut Hollow products, services or information. Such third parties from whom you have requested products, services and information will handle, store, retain, use, share and access Personal Information in accordance with the terms and conditions of their agreement(s) with you, as well as their own privacy policies, and may use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes. It is your responsibility to carefully review such terms and conditions and privacy policies, and Walnut Hollow disclaims any and all liability relating thereto.
c. Third Party Communications - Walnut Hollow also may share Personal Information with third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. Such third parties to whom we transfer Personal Information for direct marketing purposes will handle, store, retain, use, share and access Personal Information in accordance with their own privacy policies. It is your responsibility to carefully review such terms and conditions and privacy policies, and Walnut Hollow disclaims any and all liability relating thereto. If you would prefer that we do not share your Personal Information with such third parties for their direct marketing purposes, you may submit an opt-out request as described in Section 6 ("Opt-Out") below.   Please be advised – Walnut Hollow does not sell your information to ANY third party.
d. Law Enforcement; Emergencies; Compliance - Walnut Hollow reserves the right and may disclose Personal Information in the following situations as we believe to be appropriate, even though you might have requested that we don't share your information: (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to governmental requests, including requests from law enforcement and regulatory authorities; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Walnut Hollow, you or others; and (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. For example, we may, to the fullest extent the law allows, disclose Personal Information to law enforcement agencies and regulatory authorities to assist them in identifying individuals who have been or may be engaged in unlawful activities.   Use of our Services demonstrates your consent to this disclosure, if in Walnut Hollow’s sole discretion, such disclosure is necessary.
e. Assignment - We reserve the right to transfer Personal Information to a new entity or third party as part of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of some or all of our assets, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). We will notify you via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site if the third party's or new entity's treatment of Personal Information will materially differ from the treatment described in this Privacy Policy; this notice will be provided at least 30 days before such material changes take effect.
4. Updating Your Personal Information
Walnut Hollow will make an effort to keep all your Personal Information up to date when you provide it to us. You can update your account information and change your password at any time. You will find this at “My Account” in your personal Walnut Hollow account. If any of your Personal Information changes, or you identify a mistake in our records, please use the account profile page on www.walnuthollow.com , or contact us.
5. Opt-Out
You may unsubscribe to our notification services through your account profile on www.walnuthollow.com site. Simply go to your My Account page and click on “Email Preferences,”' click the box next to “I want to opt-out from all lists above and all future lists” and click “Save.”  From time to time Walnut Hollow may share Personal Information with affiliates or third parties to allow them to contact you regarding products, programs, services and promotions that we believe may be of interest to you. If you would prefer that we do not share your Personal Information with affiliates and/or third parties for such affiliates' and/or third parties' direct marketing purposes, you may submit an opt-out request by again going to your My Account page and click on “Email Preferences,”' click the box next to “I want to opt-out from all lists above and all future lists” and click “Save.”  We will comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that we will not be able to remove your Personal Information from the databases of affiliates or third parties with which we have already shared your Personal Information as of the date that we implement your opt-out request. If you wish to cease receiving marketing-related emails from any such affiliates or third parties, please contact the affiliate or third party directly or use any opt-out mechanisms provided in its marketing-related emails or privacy policy.
6. Security
Walnut Hollow seeks to have reasonable security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, although we strive to protect Personal Information about you, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through or in connection with the Services or that is stored by us. You acknowledge and agree that any information you transmit through the Services or upload for storage in connection with the Services is so transmitted or stored at your own risk. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us. (Note that if you choose to notify us via physical mail, this will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem.)
7. Protecting the Privacy of Children
Our Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 18 and are not directed at such children. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 18. Please do not register atwww.walnuthollow.com if you are under the age of 18.
8. Third Party Sites
The Services may contain links to third party websites. These linked sites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of any such linked site, or any link contained in any linked site. We provide such links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us. If you provide any Personal Information through any such third party website, your transaction will occur on such third party's website (not the Services) and the Personal Information you provide will be collected by, and controlled by the privacy policy of, that third party. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and practices of any such third parties. PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT ADDRESS THE PRIVACY OR INFORMATION PRACTICES OF ANY THIRD PARTIES.
9. Changes and Notification
We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. If our Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on the Site and we will change the 'Last Updated' date at the top of this page to reflect the date of the modification. Please check back periodically. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective upon our posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Use of the Services following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy then in effect.
10. Contact Us
Please contact us to communicate any questions or concerns.
11. Jurisdictional Issues
The Services are controlled and operated by us from the United States, and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. We do not represent or warrant that the Services, or any part of the Services, are appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Services do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit the Services' availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion.
.
Learn More
Walnut Hollow® GREW from a small, family-owned business in Dodgeville, WI to an internationally renowned wood manufacturer. Through our high industry standards and strict environmental initiatives, Walnut Hollow has created best selling wood products for the craft and hobby, outdoor sportsman and personalized home decor categories.
Our products can be found in major craft chains, independent retail stores, Internet stores, catalog companies, art stores, hobby shops and hardware stores throughout the United States, Canada and other foreign countries as well as on our websites - walnuthollow.com and walnuthollowcountry.com.
About Us
Contact Us
Customer Service
FAQs
Gallery
Privacy Policy
Terms Of Use
Site Map
©2020 Walnut Hollow® All rights reserved.
